1. randomEmail = custom.RandomData.generateRandomEmail()
5. randomFirstName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomFirstName()
9. randomLastName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomLastName()
13. randomPhone = custom.RandomData.generateRandomPhone()
17. randomAddress = custom.RandomData.generateRandomAddress()
21. randomCode = custom.RandomData.generateRandomCode()
25. openBrowser(URL)
29. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
33. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/icon-search"))
37. sendKeys(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), Keys.chord("IPHONE 12 PRO MAX 128GB GOLD", ENTER))
41. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/verify-product-iphone-12 -pro"))
45. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/btn-product - IPHONE 12 PRO MAX 128GB GOLD"))
49. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/button_Add to Cart"))
53. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"), 10)
57. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"))
61. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"))
65. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"))
69. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/field_email"), 10)
73. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/field_email"), randomEmail)
77. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/btn_continue"))
81. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_First Name"), 10)
85. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_First Name"), randomFirstName)
89. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_Last Name"), randomLastName)
93. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_mobile phone"), randomPhone)
97. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_Address"), randomAddress)
101. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_ZipPostal Code"), randomCode)
105. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_Province"))
109. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/li_Phnom Penh Capital_Province"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
113. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_Select Province"))
117. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/li_Khan Chamkar Mon_Select_Province"))
121. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_Districts"))
125. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/li_Sangkat Tonle Basak_Districts"))
129. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn-save"))
133. check(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/Billing address same as shipping"))
137. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/field_First Name"), 10)
141. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/field_First Name"), randomFirstName)
145. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/field_Last Name"), randomLastName)
149. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/field_mobile phone"), randomPhone)
153. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/field_Address"), randomAddress)
157. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/input_Province"), 5)
161. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/input_Province"), 10)
165. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/input_Province"))
169. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/li_Phnom Penh Capital_Province"), 10)
173. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/li_Phnom Penh Capital_Province"))
177. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/input_Select Province"), 10)
181. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/input_Select Province"))
185. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/li_Khan Mean Chey_1"), 10)
189. mouseOver(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/li_Khan Mean Chey"))
193. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/li_Khan Mean Chey_1"))
197. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/input_Districts"), 10)
201. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/input_Districts"))
205. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/li_Sangkat Chak Angrae Kraom"), 10)
209. mouseOver(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/li_Sangkat Chak Angrae Kraom"))
213. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/li_Sangkat Chak Angrae Kraom_1"))
217. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Billing/input_ZipPostal Code"), randomCode)
221. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/Online Payment - WeChat"))
225. check(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/Checkbox__I accept"))
229. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"))
233. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/iframe_payment_online"), 10)
237. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/iframe_payment_online"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
241. delay(10)
245. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/button_Approve"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
249. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/button_Continue shopping"), 10)
253. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/button_Continue shopping"), 0)
257. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/button_Continue shopping"))
261. takeScreenshot()
265. comment("Email      : " + randomEmail)
269. comment("First Name : " + randomFirstName)
273. comment("Last Name  : " + randomLastName)
277. comment("Phone      : " + randomPhone)
281. comment("Address    : " + randomAddress)
285. comment("Code    : " + randomCode)
289. closeBrowser()